# **†William Zhou**

Email: will3.git@gmail.com Phone: 021 026 85259

NZ Residency

Experienced Mobile developer who is passionate about building beautiful, reponsive apps. In my previous job, I was one of the core developers for several successful green field projects. In my free time, I like to work on open source projects to further my learning.

## **Skills**

Swift 9 / 10	Objective-C 9 / 10	Android 7 / 10
ASP.NET <b>4</b> / 10	Node.js <b>6</b> / 10	JavaScript 8 / 10
CoffeeScript 5 / 10	HTML, CSS <b>4</b> / 10	Jenkins <b>7</b> / 10

## Work History

## Vista Entertainment Solutions

Mobile Developer 2012-2016

Responsibilities

- \* Maintaining and extending mobile products (iOS & Android)
- \* Configuring continuous integration (Jenkins), assisting App Store releases
- \* Building several internal tools (Node.js)
- \* Maintaining app server modules (ASP.NET Web API)

## Cycles Research Institute

Research Assistant 2009-2011

Main developer for data analysis / plotting tool (BASIC) http://cyclesresearchinstitute.org/cats/

## **Education**

## University of Auckland

Bachelor of Commerce majoring in Infosys and OpsMgt

2008-2012

## **Apps**

## Vista MobileCinema

Ticketing app for cinema goers

https://itunes.apple.com/nz/app/vista-mobile/id882981768

#### Vista UsherPoint

Assist cinema ushers with crowd control

https://itunes.apple.com/nz/app/vista-usherpoint/id642694108

## Vista InTouch

Help cinema managers monitor staff and session sales https://itunes.apple.com/nz/app/vista-intouch/id642693317

## Sky Map

Star gazing app

https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/store/apps/sky-map/9wzdncrdnvz0

# **Projects**

## Voskel

3d voxel art creation tool http://voskel.herokuapp.com

## Meow (2016 Global game jam)

Typing game, with cats play now: http://nychinn.github.io/meow

## injectour

Lightweight injector, inspired by angular js https://www.npmjs.com/package/injectour

## cpr2

Retro style colour picker https://www.npmjs.com/package/cpr2

## edger

Generate hard edges for voxel data https://www.npmjs.com/package/edger

References available upon request